This is how I'll become.
Supreme Commander!
A hero!
This is my story!
In the dark darkness,
I'm one and one, I'm one and one,
I'm tired of crying!
I'm a dream of a dream?
But now, when I was your
friend, I would bring you back.
I'm not always gonna go up here,
but I don't want to be the only one.
I'll be the only one.
I'll be the only one that
I'll be the only one day.
I'll be the only one day long.
Please don't go anywhere,
fast, then share me the world.
Let's make the new world.
I'll never experience the world.
We will be the only world.
I've got this!
Nice one, Commander!
Boom!
I'm very disappointed.
I waited patiently, yet only
two targets came out to play.
Where are the rest of you?
Two targets with myself included.
Is he after the commanders?
This fight will be over.
In the mere blink of an eye!
That was the strength of their leader?
I expected more from those little pests.
If you could stay still,
that would be great.
You dare attempt to kick me?
How arrogant of you!
My flesh is as strong as steel.
Now block this!
I am invincible!
I'm hurt? Impossible.
Incredible.
She's taking on a humanoid.
Lady 10 is very talented.
She can escape anything
because of her ability.
but she doesn't actually need to run away.
Both commanders came up with a plan to
wipe out an invading army in no time flat,
and they did it all in their heads!
Oh my god, Lady Ken!
Lady Ken, you're so freaking hot!
Oh my god!
Grat!
All right, fine!
Well, this time I'll simply have to...
blow you to pieces!
Ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Good luck avoiding that one!
What? Is she?
Just relax.
That's the end of her.
Huh?
Did he really think it was over?
She teleported me by tossing me?
The perfect decision.
Lady Ten has the godlike ability to
manipulate space around her, aptly named...
Ame no mitori.
If I rip apart the fabric of space,
your defenses don't do you much good.
An entire swarm of Shuki gone.
All of the commanders
are brilliant like that.
They're obviously on a different level.
And Miss Kyoka wants to be the
Supreme Commander in charge of them?
Sounds like an awfully ambitious goal.
True, but I'm going to be the
next Supreme Commander in line.
I guess I don't have to worry.
All right, hunt the
stragglers and take them out!
Yes, ma 'am!
I can't just stand around
gawking at Miss Kyoka.
I made up my mind to be a hero in Mato!
We exterminated the Shuki army.
But according to Nei's report, there
were other enemy generals present.
And yet there was no sign of them.
We searched as thorough as possible,
but still came up empty-handed.
Maybe what happened is all of them
got squashed in that big blast.
I'm not so sure.
They were very peculiar.
I'm sorry, everyone.
Even with the power of foresight,
I detected the enemy too late.
Hey, it happens.
They probably used some
sort of cloaking ability.
You detected them before
they started attacking us.
Meaning, you circumvented
any potential for an ambush.
You did your job well, so
don't dwell on the negative.
Precisely. Yay!
Little Slave, You really
stole the show out there.
Oh, I don't know about that.
You were way more impressive
than me, Miss Izumo.
Mr. Yuki!
I witnessed your performance
on the battlefield!
So now I know that boys can
be talented sometimes too!
If you don't mind, can
I have your autograph?
Me?
You see, now you've got a fan.
Hey.
What do you want?
About earlier.
Thank you for saving my life.
Yeah, well, you are an Azuma.
If I'd let the enemy defeat you, it
would bring shame upon the family.
That is the only reason why I saved you.
Of course, if you're saying that you
felt the weight of your own inadequacies.
I'd graciously train them out of you.
So come back home and.
The 7th Squadron is my home.
Writing up a report is
going to be a challenge.
As for the exhibition match...
Mm-hmm.
I suppose we'll call it a draw for now.
It's unfortunate.
I was really looking
forward to our one-on-one.
Yes, me too.
Well, we'll be heading out now.
Bye-bye, ladies!
See you later.
Well I'm beat I need a
nice refreshing bath.
Is this supposed to be my reward
weren't you the one who asked for this?
So indecent well he did slay a
substantial number of Shuuki today.
Miss Kyoka too?
I get both at the same time?
It's the price of my ability.
Every single time.
Yet I'm always surprised. Wait a minute.
She's going to get in
the hot spring with me?
Freaking pervert.
Take off your damn clothes!
Oh, uh, yes ma 'am!
I wasn't exactly sure what to
expect when we stripped down naked,
but evidently he wanted a good scrap down.
I just thought it would be kind
of nice to freshen up a little.
Well, it's basically the
same thing as bathing a dog,
so there's no reason to be embarrassed.
I can't understand anything you
say when you talk that fast.
Yuki, your body is more
tired than usual, isn't it?
Mm, it is.
Two masters at once took a lot out of me.
So it makes you strong, but
it's not to be used lightly.
Right.
We learned to utilize the
skill in a practical way,
and we'll need to continue to explore
its possibilities in the future.
But for the time being,
you should get some rest.
The dorm's hot spring is
great for curing fatigue.
The lens naysaw!
Look like this!
It's amazing as always!
My magnum opus!
Sure, it's good, but the
art style is kind of...
They'll make an official
composite sketch at HQ later on.
Neither of them are the humanoid
we encountered last time.
The one that looks like my sister
how come she wasn't with them?
Maybe they're a different squad
or is there some other reason?
Oh, my God.
So this is the Sixth Squadron's dorm.
All of the dormitories look
identical on the outside.
I noticed that when we
visited the Fifth Squadron.
For the most part, yes.
Though the interiors
tend to differ slightly.
Welcome to the Sixth Squadron dorm.
Thanks for making the trek.
A little change of scenery never hurts.
Did he run into any
trouble on your way over?
Took down some Shuki in
route, but that's it.
It was business as usual in Mato.
Tenka and I need to have a meeting.
For now, these are my orders.
Get properly acquainted
with the Sixth Squadron.
A few members went out on an
expedition, so they won't be joining us.
But the rest of the girls
are still here in the dorm,
so feel free to take a look around.
Thank you.
And Yuki, as we discussed
this morning... Yes.
As the 7th Squad's caretaker, I
will help out in any way I can.
Unfortunately, our caretaker
isn't available at the moment.
It's just until they return this evening.
My apologies.
Not a problem.
As part of the Demon Defense Force,
we've got to have each other's backs.
Wouldn't you agree?
Right.
I'll be counting on you.
Uh...
Right!
Leave it to me!
All right, first things first, cleaning.
Or it would be.
But this place is pretty clean already.
And here I was getting all amped up.
Hm? Oh.
This stain.
Judging by the feel of it,
Formula 5 might work better
than just plain old baking soda.
Hmm, or maybe...
So many choices!
Next up is laundry!
Breathe.
Just breathe.
You do the 7th Squad's
laundry all the time.
Never mind.
I'm still not used to it.
I wonder what Yuki is up to right now.
Oh man, I wish I could have gone with him.
I told myself I'd get him to like me more.
If anything, I should be using
this time for self-improvement.
I guess I'll start by tidying up.
Himari's big sister's room.
I wonder what she'll say when she sees me.
Anyone home?
Hello?
She's not here.
I guess I'll just leave this in her room.
Pardon me?
What the...
Sahara Wakasa?
Why is she asleep in the living room?
And in her underwear, no less.
I can't let her catch
a cold, so I'll just...
Does she think I'm her pillow?
I have to bail before someone sees me.
No, no, you're not going anyway. Oh, yeah.
This is the girl who wrestled like
a pro in the exhibition match.
Either way, I've got to get free.
Now behave yourself.
And though I wished for
escape, I was unable to escape.
So, eventually, I stopped
thinking and gave in.
Aw, sorry, my bad.
I completely forgot the 7th Squadron
was supposed to come visit today. Yeah.
Huh?
Hey, Himari, what's up?
I'm waiting until she's
done to speak to her.
Does Yachiho do this regularly? Mm-hmm.
She trained like that before
the exhibition match, too.
She's pushing herself
even harder nowadays.
Hey, do you look up to Yachi?
I mean, since she's
your big sister and all.
Her personality is terrible, but she's
successful academically and athletically.
I've always thought I could
learn a thing or two from her.
Personally,
I'm a fan of the theory that
someone's Peach ability is
based on their human nature
and knowledge they've acquired.
So in your case,
your desire to learn from Yachi is the
reason why learning became your ability.
And the same goes for Yachi's
skill to control time.
It stems from her desire to spend
time with her little sister.
Makes sense, don't you think?
Hmm.
I think that you are making
a lot of assumptions.
Aw, but it might be nice if you talk
to her a little more often, right?
Huh? Yeah.
Your big sister's cool.
Here I guess she is.
What can't hear you you
need to check your attitude!
What a relief looks like they're
getting along better already? Yeah.
Though,
I suppose showing her Yachi's room would
be the most efficient way to solve this.
Perhaps it would be best
to keep that part a secret.
Track down the humanoid Shuki.
Correct.
We've seen no movement from the
humanoid since this latest attack.
So instead of waiting around, I
think we should make the first move.
Yes, good point.
That large crater.
My team encountered a
vast group of Shuki there.
It's also where we first
engaged a humanoid.
That's where we should
start our investigation.
Okay.
I don't have any issues with that call.
I'm curious.
How many more of these
things do you think exist?
We've confirmed a total of four so far.
But you already eliminated
one of those four humanoids.
I'm not certain.
To be honest with you, I didn't get the
feeling that we truly defeated that being.
Glad to see you've made
a full recovery, Rairen.
Seriously, that was a
very close encounter.
it's a good thing you have me i
could have kept fighting after that
the battle was lost when you let them
raise your army to the ground i agree
with shikoku's assessment let us review
shall we in order to evaluate the enemy's
capabilities i fought the third squadron
it was a piece of cake but their
commander wasn't with them at the time so
the purpose of this recent endeavor was to
experience the commander's strength
firsthand but they blew my expectations out
of the water it appears that your plan to
use our resources and launch a full-scale
attack on the defense force was trash
wait just a second they may be a tough
organization but I know they can be beaten
which one of us do you think
is right Jouryuu. Shikoku.
Of course.
Now that that's settled, we're
going with my plan this time.
We will launch an attack once
we've gathered all eight people.
Until then, we operate from the shadows.
The eight of us will be
together soon enough.
Very well.
However, I hate it when you
use the phrase eight people!
We are not filthy humans!
Don't degrade us like that!
My mistake.
Shikoku, you're interested
in the humans, aren't you?
Humans are fascinating creatures.
You might say they're more
complex than I imagined.
I just can't get enough.
I suppose that concludes today's meeting.
Did you have anything else?
Just one thing regarding personnel.
What is it?
Little Slave, do you mind if I keep him?
Let's do it.
She can heal the wounds
of anyone inside too,
which means she's always in high demand?
for things like combat training
and exhibition matches.
Ms.
Geena's also a big fan
of the Defense Force
and collects the
autographs of its members.
Anyways, next time, promise nay, remember.